{
    "id": "b07d1b9646614068a86ef782979ec471",
    "title": "Conditional Clauses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. run into Jake, tell him that he owes me 100 dollars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "could",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I had another 1000 dollars, I ………………… a car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can buy",
                "could buy",
                "could have bought"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If he should be late, we ……………….. to go without him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will have",
                "would have",
                "could have"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What would you do if you ………………… to lose your job?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. to move a bit, I could sit here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "have",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Had I realized what you intended, I ………………….. this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not permit",
                "would not permit",
                "would not have permitted"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Were she my daughter, I …………………… her wear that mini-frock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not let",
                "would not let",
                "would not have let"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. finish early, give me a ring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "happen to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will get up earlier if there ………………… a good reason to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It would be nice if you …………………. me a few dollars.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lend",
                "lent",
                "would lend"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}